export const FLASHCARDS = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'Who is the first man and Prophet Allah created?',
    answer: 'Adam (AS)',
    options: ['Yusuf (AS)', 'Ibrahim (AS)', 'Adam (AS)'],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      'After Allah created Adam (AS), Allah ordered all the angels and jinns to bow down to Adam (AS). Everyone listened except _____ ?',
    answer: 'Shaytaan',
    options: ['Angels', 'Musa (AS)', 'Shaytaan'],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'How did Allah test Adam (AS) and his wife, Hawwa?',
    answer: 'Allah told them not to eat from a tree.',
    options: [
      'Allah told them not to sleep.',
      'Allah told them not to eat from a tree.',
      'Allah told them not to pray.',
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      'Prophet Nuh (AS) told him people to worship only Allah instead of _________.',
    answer: 'Idols',
    options: ['Trees', 'Animals', 'Idols'],
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      'Allah told Prophet Nuh (AS) to build a big _______ because a flood was coming.',
    answer: 'Boat',
    options: ['Boat', 'House', 'Statue'],
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      'Which prophet was saved from a hot fire when Allah made the fire cold for him?',
    answer: 'Ibrahim (AS)',
    options: ['Muhammad (SAW)', 'Yusuf (AS)', 'Ibrahim (AS)'],
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      'Allah told Prophet Ibrahim (AS) to travel with his family until they came to a place near 2 hills called ____',
    answer: 'Safa and Marwa',
    options: ['Makkah and Medina', 'Safa and Marwa'],
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      'When Haajar was looking for water she between Safa to Marwa 7 times. How did Allah reward her?',
    answer: 'Zamzam water started gushing out of the ground.',
    options: [
      'It started to rain.',
      'She found a river.',
      'Zamzam water started gushing out of the ground.',
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'Allah tested Prophet Ibrahim (AS) by telling him to __________.',
    answer: 'Sacrifice his son.',
    options: [
      'Sacrifice his son.',
      'Not to eat from a tree.',
      'Talk to Firawn',
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      'Which holiday do we celebrate to remember Prophet Ibrahim (AS) sacrificing a sheep instead of his son?',
    answer: 'Eid-ul-Adha',
    options: ['Eid-ul-Adha', 'Eid-ul-Fitr', 'Thanksgiving', 'New Years'],
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'Which prophet was swallowed by a whale?',
    answer: 'Yunus (AS)',
    options: ['Yunus (AS)', 'Musa (AS)', 'Yusuf (AS)'],
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'How did Allah save Musa (AS) and his people from Firawn?',
    answer: 'Allah caused the sea to split.',
    options: [
      'Allah gave them a boat.',
      'Allah gave them Zamzam water.',
      'Allah caused the sea to split.',
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'Which prophet spoke as a baby?',
    answer: 'Isa (AS)',
    options: ['Isa (AS)', 'Muhammad (SAW)', 'Adam (AS)'],
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'What book did Allah reveal to Prophet Muhammad (SAW)?',
    answer: "Qur'an",
    options: ['Tawrat', 'Injeel', "Qur'an"],
  },
];
